Go on, then. However,
if I detect even a trace of deceit
in your words, I shall end your life.
Fine by me.
You should do what you think is right.
As long as you're not just
blindly following orders.
I say that because you
won't know the difference.
You don't realize it.
But everything you've
been fighting for as a
knight was planted in
your head by someone else.
Everyone knows this story,
that you knights were called down
from heaven by Administrator,
the pontifex of the church,
to maintain order in this
world and dole out justice.
But being summoned's the
oldest memory you knights have.
Think back.
Do you remember what heaven was like?
Or your childhood?
Or your parents?
Well, no.
Of course not.
Our memories of heaven have been sealed.
I was told the goddess Stacia does
that the moment we are summoned here.
You get the part about your
memories being sealed, right?
But Stacia isn't the
one who did that to you.
It was the Pontifex, and she
didn't block memories of heaven,
but your memories of here.
All you knights were born and raised
human, right here in this world.
You have a human name.
Alice Zuberg.
Your folks raised you in a tiny
village up north called Rulid.
When you were eleven,
you went to explore a cave that ran through
the End Mountains to the Dark Territory.
When you came out the other side,
you touched the ground on accident.
You trespassed on the Dark Territory.
You broke the law.
Alice Zuburg.
I have a human name?
The End Mountains. Unruled.
I cannot remember.
None of it.
Yeah, well, don't force yourself.
You'll end up like Eldrie.
It is too late to stop now. Go on.
Tell me everything.
Thank you
so
much for watching.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
Your father's the village elder of Rulid.
His name's Gosfut Zuburg.
I don't know your mom's name, but like I
told you before, you have a little sister.
I met her.
Her name's Selka.
Selka?
Ever since you were taken away by
the church, she's been worried sick.
When you lived in Rulid, you
were a sister in training?
and really good at the sacred arts.
Now,
Selka's a sister in training, too,
and she's working hard to get
as good at the arts as you.
Your goal, as you stated,
was not treason against the Church,
but to bring the Pontifex to justice
and protect the human realm, yes?
Yeah, that's the plan.
And yet, we Integrity Knights have a
duty to protect the human realm as well.
We defend it against invasion by
the Dark Territory at all costs.
If you manage to defeat all
of the Integrity Knights,
as well as slay the
Pontifex herself, what then?
There would be no one
to protect this realm.
Well, let me ask you this.
If the Dark Territory invades and all
of you knights hit him full force,
that's only going to be, what,
a little over 30 of you?
Do you honestly think that's
enough to beat him back?
Prime Senator, you need to talk to
the Pontifex about the Dark Territory.
Every day their army gets bigger, it's
a matter of time before they attack.
I'm worried there's not enough of
us knights to take them all on.
That's your problem!
You are Integrity Knights, so use your
brains and figure it out yourself!
We are done talking about this!
Trust in the Pontifex, do as
you're told, and all will be fine!
Honestly!
Actually, you're right.
Even Unc - or rather,
Commander Bercoli had misgivings
about our numbers compared to theirs.
Aside from us knights,
the Human Empire does not have an army
at the ready should war break out.
I know, and the reason we don't have
an army is Administrator's fault.
You know why that is?
It's because she's scared that
if the people had weapons,
they could all rise up against her.
If a war happens, the nobles are
supposed to protect the weak.
But she let the upper class get lazy.
And corrupt.
They just care about themselves now.
This world's running out of
time, but it still has a chance.
If we can get the word out before the
armies of the Dark show up, we can fight.
With enough people, we
can build our own army.
That is impossible. An army?
You just said how corrupt the nobles are.
They would protect their own
interests before anyone else.
Yeah, some of them.
But they're just a small group of people.
Not everyone thinks like they do.
The lower class nobles and commoners
would join the fight in a heartbeat.
The commoners, too?
Uh-huh.
All we do is hand out the weapons you
guys have got stashed here in the tower.
Then, we teach everyone the same sword
skills and sacred arts you knights know.
If we do that, we could build
an army in a year or so.
Thing is, at this point, it can't happen
if the Pontifex is still in charge.
You know what scares her more
than the forces of the dark?
It's people having free will.
If she can't have an army loyal
to her, there won't be an army.
So I say, we throw a coup.
If we can bring down Administrator,
we'll free all the people.
Then we can use the time we got
left to train them all to fight.
And with any luck, we'll have an
army big enough to stop the invasion.
The fact these minions are here,
that alone is proof of the contempt
that Pontifex has for us knights,
her most loyal servants, and the people.
All right, then.
I'll help, under one condition.
I want your word that when I regain my
memory, I will get to see my sister, Selka,
again.
Yeah, of course. You will.
It's just, when you do get it back,
you're not going to be who
you are right now anymore.
Alice Synthesis 30 The
Integrity Knight will be gone,
and all the memories you
have now will be gone.
You'll go back to being Alice Zuburg,
the girl from a village up north.
Selka. Selka.
I cannot remember her face, or her
voice, but when I say her name,
it is familiar to me.
My lips, throat, and heart.
They remember.
I used to say that name
all the time. Selka. Selka.
I know in my soul.
I have a family.
A father, a mother, a sister.
My own flesh and blood.
Somewhere out there.
Under the stars.
When you said before that we knights were
not called but created by the Pontifex,
it confirmed what I have suspected.
This body, the one I have been
occupying for the past six years.
Was stolen from another.
I know that now.
Therefore, I shall return what was stolen.
It is what Selka, her parents,
and your friend would want.
I am sure you would want
that as well, yes? Oh yeah.
But first, I have one favor to ask. What?
If you would,
before you return the
original Alice's memory,
I would like you to accompany
me to Rulid village.
I wish to visit there, but
I do not want to be seen.
Just observe, and if you would,
please point Selka and my family out.
Grant me that, and I
would be most grateful.
Sure.
You got it.
I swear.
Before we restore your memory, I'll
take you back to Rulid to see him.
You had better.
From this moment onward,
I shall protect the human empire
and its citizens in earnest.
I, Alice Synthesis 30, hereby abandon
my rank as an Integrity Knight.
What's wrong?
Alice!
Kitty.
Let me see.
It looks like a barcode.
What the hell?
My eye it burns so I
see symbols words don't
think about anything
hurry clear your mind.
What's happening is when
you defied the church
it triggered some kind of mental barrier.
That's what's causing the pain and if you
keep thinking about it
your eye will explode?
How cruel.
Not only are my memories
zampered with, but my will.
Even that.
Whoever did this is evil.
Tell me, is the one who burned these,
these words onto my eye, was it her?
Was it the Pontifex?
No, I don't think it's her.
It's a creator, watching
this world from the outside.
Like a god, but not like the
ones in your creation story.
God, we knights are their servants.
We have fought endlessly in their name.
We protect their world, yet
they do not even trust us.
They took my memories
of my family and sister.
They cast this diabolical hex on me!
To ensure my servitude to them.
I am not a puppet!
Even if I am the creation
of another entity.
My mind is my own.
And I will protect this world
and all the people in it.
Regardless what they want!
That is my mission!
Alice...
Kirito, to break this,
I need you to hold me.
Sure.
Hear me, Administrator,
and you heartless gods.
For the sake of my mission, and
this world, I hereby renounce you!
EUGEO? EUGEO?
You must be cold.
Come on, it's warmer here. Hurry!
Mother, is it really you?
Of course it is.
Now who else would I be?
Where's father?
And my brothers? Where are they?
Silly child, don't you remember?
You killed them all.
What happened to me?
How did I get here?
The last thing I remember was
fighting Bercouli from the legend.
Then a little man appeared.
Chudelkin.
And after that, I woke up.
But where?
Is this the top floor of
the central cathedral?
If this is the top
floor, that must be her.
No, Eugeo! Run!
She's the Pontifex.
Administrator.
Now's my chance.
No, I can't use the dagger on her.
I was saving it for Alice.
You two! Run!
You pitiful thing.
Pitiful?
That's right.
You look so miserable.
Just like a flower,
withering away in a pot.
A flower? Me? Yes.
If you could see yourself, you'd agree.
You look parched. Starving. For what?
For love. Love?
No way.
You're wrong.
I am loved by lots of people.
You've never known what it
means to be loved by anyone.
That's why you're so sad.
That's not true.
There's my mom.
She loved me.
Whenever I had a nightmare
and I couldn't sleep,
she'd hold me and sing lullabies
to make me feel better.
Perhaps she did.
But was that love meant only for you?
You know it wasn't.
It was what she had left over after
sharing it with your brothers.
No way.
She loved me.
She did.
I was the one she loved the most.
You wanted her love all for yourself,
but she loved the others more.
That's why you hate them so.
Your father, your brothers,
they stole it. Stop it. Liar.
I don't hate my father or my brothers.
I am not jealous.
Oh, but you are.
Why else would you attack that boy?
What boy?
The one who came between you and
the red-haired girl who loved you.
Who loved only you.
When the boy kidnapped her and tried
to defile her, you wanted to kill him.
You hated him because he took
something that was yours.
You're wrong.
That's not...
I didn't attack Raios
because I was jealous of him.
And yet here you are, alone.
No one loves you.
They decided they don't need
you anymore and abandoned you.
By now, they've forgotten about you. No.
You're lying.
There's still someone who wants me.
Alice, that's it.
Alice still needs me.
Are you sure?
Does she love you?
Does she love you and only you?
You seem to have forgotten.
I can help you remember.
You have buried the memory deep within
your heart, but I can unearth it.
I haven't seen Kirito
and Alice all morning.
Where could they be?
Alice...
But, like, what if he comes
looking? Let's go back.
But we're almost finished. Let's stay.
Just a bit longer. Please?
No.
This isn't real.
It didn't happen.
I told you so.
Now do you believe me?
She doesn't love you.
Not just you, at any rate. Poor thing.
In fact, she didn't have any
love for you from the start.
I'm nothing like that girl, Eugeo.
I would be happy to love you.
I'd give you all of it.
Just you and no one else.
No one else.
Now, come closer, Eugeo.
I will show you what love is, and
you can love me as much as you want.
If you give me all of your love, I will
give you all the love I have in return!
And the deeper your love is for me, the
more of its pleasures will I then show you?
Pleasures beyond your wildest dreams.
Is that really what love is about?
A thing you trade?
Like money?
Is that all it is?
No, Eugeo!
That's not true!
That isn't love!
Don't be fooled, Eugeo!
Love isn't like that.
You don't give your love
to get something in return?
You do!
I know what you want.
You want to forget all of your sadness
and make love to me till the end of time.
You will, but not yet.
First, my dear, I must
have proof of your love.
You will trust only in me and
offer all of yourself to me.
When I tell you what words
to say, you will say them.
Now, initiate the sacred arts.
System call.
Good.
Now repeat after me.
Remove core protection.
Remove?
Am I doing the right thing?
Core.
I don't want to be sad anymore.
I don't want to be alone.
That's it.
Good.
You're almost done.
Come into me.
Into eternal stasis.
Protection.
Next time. Synthesis.